Hello.
In this next lecture, we're going to be fixing our player character's camera.
If I go play.
And just play my game.
Over time, you may have noticed the game gets lighter and lighter and it kind of makes things a bit
hard to see in order to fix this.
If we go over to our player blueprint.
And select the camera.
And go to details and look for brightness.
Just check min and max brightness.
The lower we make these values, the brighter the game is going to be.
And the higher we make these values, the darker the game is going to be.
So I make this 0.1 and this 0.1 and I go compile and play.
My game is going to look very, very bright.
However, if I make this look like two and two.
Then my game is going to have a normal level of brightness.
So this looks fine and it's not going to become brighter and brighter over time.
So with this, we fix our camera issue.
Hello, guys.
I want to show you another issue that you may be experiencing.
If I jump onto this platform.
Sometimes my character can become locked in their jumping animation.
I'm going to explain why this happens and how we can fix this.
So if we close this and go over to your character's animation blueprint, open it up.
Now we have a transition from our characters idols that run animation to their jumping animation.
So what's happening is my character is falling in the air and then they enter this jumping animation.
However, sometimes my character can land before they reach their falling animation, so they get locked
up in this jumping animation to fix this at a node from jumping to run.
And the condition for this, we just want to drag in our slap reference drag of here and look for is
walking.
And just connect this into here and go compile.
That should fix that issue and you shouldn't have it occur anymore.
Hello.
There's one more issue I want to fix with my camera.
If I could play since I adjusted my camera to be further away.
Everything looks kind of blurry, so my characters idol animation looks kind of blurry.
And if I move, everything kind of looks blurry.
And my player character, in order to fix this, go over to edit and set product settings and look for
anti then under anti analyzing method select fast or none.
I'm just going to select none.
And now I close this and go play.
My sprite should not look blurry and everything should look normal.